A Finding Aid to the Donald Saff papers and Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1710, 1800-2013 bulk 1965-2010, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Saff Tech Arts Records, circa 1970-2013; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 22.2 Linear feet Boxes 10-32, 34; .640 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
  - Artist Files, circa 1970-2010; 2.2; Archival Resource Key; 15.2 Linear feet Boxes 12-27, 33; 0.64 Gigabytes ER010-ER011
    - James Rosenquist, Archival Resource Key
      - Exhibition, Archival Resource Key
        - Palias de Chailliot (Unrealized Ceiling Mural), circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Loan, Taejon Expo 93' Welcome to the Waterplanet, Shipping, Insurance, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Rosenquist v. North American Watch Corp., Nancy Farage Esq., circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Printed Material, Invitations and Press Clippings, circa 1993-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Ed Ruscha, 1971-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - George Segal, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Kiki Smith, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Frank Stella, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - James Turrell, Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, circa 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Exhibition, Knoedler & Co. (Nov.-Dec. 1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Exhibition, Setagaya Art Museum (Aug.-Oct. 1998), circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 20-22)
      - Loan, Neuberger Museum of Art (Sep.-Dec. 1994), circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Loan, Montclair Art Museum, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Loan, Contemporary Art Center, Art Tower Mito, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Inventory, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Sales, circa 1993-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 27)
      - Fabrication, Metal Masters, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 28)
      - Turrell World Tour, circa 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 29)
      - 2007 Working Values, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Printed Material, Miscellaneous, circa 1993-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Business Records, circa 1980-2011; 2.3; Archival Resource Key; 3.7 Linear feet Boxes 27-31, 34
    Business records include inventory, sales and consignments including multiple artists, regular business relationships including Knoedler & Co., appointment books, fabrication schedules, employee timesheets, and legal and insurance documents including claims, disputes and leasing information, as well as the pursuit of trademarks on production techniques.
    - Knoedler & Co., Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, General, circa 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, Marcella Consolini, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, Carol Corey, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, Ann Freedman, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, Sueyen Locks, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, Judy Ringer, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, Larry Rubin, circa 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, Peter Sansone, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 39)
      - Consignments, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Employment (DJS), circa 1990, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Expenses, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Inventory, Archival Resource Key
      - DS001-DS175 (Artists A-M), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - DS176-DS374 (Artists M-R), circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - DS375-DS480, DJS001-DJS091, SP1-8, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Inventory 1994-1998 Taxes, circa 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Inventory with Values (Oct. 1994), Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Inventory by Artist (Aug. 24, 2000), Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Inventory, circa 1993-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Auction Inventory, circa 2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous Inventory, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Consignments, Archival Resource Key
      - Consignments (Camino -Greenberg), circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Consignments (Greenfield-Knoedler), circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Consignments (Knoedler, cont. - Weber), circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Sales, Archival Resource Key
      - Invoicing Information, circa 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 16-18)
      - Invoicing, STA Employee Storage, circa 1991-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Invoices, JP DeAndino, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Invoices, Seth Abraham, circa 1992, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Invoices, Berggruen Gallery, circa 1990, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - Invoices, Paulette and Mel Blumenthal, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Invoices, Senator and Mrs. Bradley, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Invoices, Betsy Burton, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Invoices, Abbey Butler, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Invoices, Joanne Campbell, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Invoices, Joanne Campbell, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - Invoices, Mathieu Carriere, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Invoices, N. Castleman, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Invoices, Rosalie Davison, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Invoices, Nancy Dubofsky, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Invoices, DC Heath and Company, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Invoices, Larry Evans, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Invoices, Kaj Forsblom, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Invoices, Arie Genger, circa 1991-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Invoices, Knoedler & Co., circa 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Invoices, Kodansha Ltd., circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Invoices, Oscar Kolin, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Invoices, La Marie Tranier Gallery, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Invoices, Torsten Lilja, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Invoices, Locks Gallery, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Invoices, William Lowenberg, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Invoices, Cargill MacMillan, Jr., circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Invoices, Alex Meyerovich, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Invoices, National Gallery of Art, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Invoices, Jonathan Novak, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Invoices, Denis Ochi, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Invoices, Mr. & Mrs. Murray Pergament, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Invoices, Posner Gallery, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - Invoices, Schmidt/Dean Gallery, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Invoices, Elliott Singer, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Invoices, William F. Smith Fine Arts Adjuster (Blum Institute), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Invoices, Sash Spencer, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Invoices, Michael E. Thomas, circa 1993-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Invoices, Fiorella Urbinetti, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - Invoices, Joni Weyl, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - Invoices, Bjorn Wetterling, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Invoices, Donald Zucker, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Auction Results, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 32-33)
      - Accounting, Betty Satchell Everngam, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - Sales Quotations, Various Artsts, circa 1999-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - STA Financial Statements (Dec. 31, 1997), Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - STA Sales Report, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - STA Sales Report 1992-1994, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - STA Financial Statements (Dec. 31, 1997), Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - STA Sales (1990-1997), circa 1996, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - STA Sales and Accounting, circa 1992-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Financial (Knoedler & Co., Miscellaneous Artists), circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Production Reports, Archival Resource Key
      - Production Schedule (Fall/Winter 1991), circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - Production Records (1992), circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 34-36)
      - Production Records (1993), circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 37-38)
      - Production Records (1994-1995), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 39)
      - Production Records (1994-1995), circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - Appointments and Travel, Archival Resource Key
      - Appointment Calendars, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Appointment Calendars, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Appointment Calendars, circa 1999-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Appointment Calendars, circa 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Appointment Calendars, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Appointment Calendars, circa 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Appointment Calendars, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Appointment Calendars, Printouts, circa 1998-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Donald Saff Planner, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Donald Saff Travel, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Donald Saff Travel (ROCI), circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Donald Saff Itinerary, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Donald Saff Itinerary, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Donald Saff Itinerary, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Donald Saff Itinerary, circa 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Donald Saff Itinerary, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Donald Saff Itinerary, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Timesheets, circa 1998-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 20-21)
    - Fabrication, Archival Resource Key
      - Brushtron Process Manual, circa 1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Golden Artist Color, Orders and Samples, circa 1988-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Crate Labels, Masters, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Framing, circa 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Honeycomb Panels, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Kaleidoscope Research Material, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Microwave Sensors, circa 1990s-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Nazdar Company Pigment Supplies, circa 1990-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Pigments, circa 1989-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Article, "Producing Tasche Wash Effects in Screenprinting..." by N. Semenoff, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - Silk Fabric, circa 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Spray Guns and Brushtronic Plating, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - Article, "Waterless Lithography" by N. Semenoff, circa 1990, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - Color and Wax Samples, circa 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - Paint Samples, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Paint Samples, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Folder 1-3)
      - Paint Samples on Supports, Frames, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 34, Item 4-7)
    - Insurance and Legal, Archival Resource Key
      - Accident Settlement, STA Vehicle 1993, circa 1993-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Archplan Inc. Field Report, Facility Maintenance STA, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Affidavit, Staff Trade Secrets, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Agreement for Construction of Nylon Structure, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Appraisers, Silverman and Associates, circa 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Appraisal and Tax Court Case re: Estate of Arnold O. Levine, circa 1987-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Copyright Registration, Various Works, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Commercial Lease Termination, Shop Appraisal and Sale (206 Pier Street), circa 1991-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Dispute and Settlement, Alfred Kren, Austin Art Consortium, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Insurance STA, Acordia Northeast, Chubb, circa 1997-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Insurance STA Renewal, Chubb, circa 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Insurance Claim, Staff, circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Incorporating Documents STA, Business Model, 1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Promissory Note, STA Startup, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Saff & Co. Operating Agreement, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Saff Tech Arts Property Environmental Assessment, circa 2001-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Saff Tech Arts Lease Agreement, Westin Enterprises, 1992, 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Valuation, Theodore W. Keele Estate, circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 18-19)
  - Printed Material, circa 1988-1999; 2.4; Archival Resource Key; 0.5 Linear feet Boxes 31-32
    Collected printed material is primarily clippings on subjects such as the art market and galleries, as well as individual artists.
    - Clippings, Saff Tech Arts, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, Galleries, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Clippings, Art Market, circa 1988-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Clippings, Various Artists, circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 23-24)
    - Clippings, Miscellaneous Topics, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Clippings, Miscellaneous Topics, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, Various Artists, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 2-3)